

## **My Contact**

☐ littlehitesh1995@gmail.com

( 7976362349, 7733951048

Jaipur, Rajasthan

www.comingsoon.com

### **Hard Skill**

- · Excel and Data analysis
- SAP, PaGOS
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Php
- · Quality Analysis

#### **Soft Skill**

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- Rajasthan University
   Masters in Commerce
   Completed in 2017
- Rajasthan University
   Bachlore in Commerce
   Completed in 2015

### **Achievements**

All India Radio - Announcer First Prize in Badminton Star Sports - Contracts

# HITESH BHARGAVA

## **Managing Operations**

#### **About Me**

Detail-orientated managing operations with 5 years of professional experience. At Ubuy Technologies, I implemented policy, planning, and strategy to improve turnover and sale. Passionate about leading operations for Company, where I can use my skills to improve operations for the benefit of the stakeholders.

## **Professional Experience**

Ubuy Technologies | Operations management 2019 - Present

- Lead, motivate, and support a large team within a time-sensitive and demanding environment, including career development plans for direct reports and problem resolution
- Manage data collection for the updating of metrics to achieve productivity targets, reduce cost per unit, eliminate errors, and deliver excellent customer service
- Partner with cross-functional teams to improve proprietary tools and systems
- Work closely with legal and safety departments to ensure that activities remain compliant
- Oversee materials and inventory
- Conduct budget reviews and report cost plans to upper management

# Bosch | Warehouse Supervisor 2017 - 2019

- Recruit, select, orient, coach and motivate employees. Produce reports and statistics regularly (IN/OUT status report, dead stock report etc)
- Strategically manage warehouse in compliance with company's policies and vision
- Oversee receiving, warehousing, distribution and maintenance operations. Setup layout and ensure efficient space utilization
- Prepare annual budget. Liaise with clients, suppliers and transport companies
- Plan work rotas, assign tasks appropriately and appraise results
- Recruit, select, orient, coach and motivate employees. Produce reports and statistics regularly (IN/OUT status report, dead stock report etc)

# Ericsson | Facilities Coordinators 04/2017 - 11/2017

- Manage end to end travel plans pan India efficiently and costeffectively – Employees and Cab Service Provider.
- Negotiate on best rates through vendors every time there is a travel occurrence.
- Communicate with the person travelling regularly to keep them updated on logistics.
- Manage emergency changes/cancellations in a professional and calm manner
- Handle all incoming travel requests and the processes that follow after.
- Update HR on travel/leaves to be properly recorded.